export const homeFaq = [
    {
        question:"What are included and excluded in the plan?",
        answer:"The plan includes access to legal advice, consultations, drafting, representing the case in court that are within the scope of your chosen plan.",
    },
    {
        question:"Why is the plan pricing so affordable while lawyers outside charge so high?",
        answer:"Medence provides affordable pricing by leveraging a scalable model that enables us to offer legal services at a lower cost while maintaining high-quality expertise. Our focus is on providing value to customers without the high overhead costs associated with traditional law firms.",
    },
    {
        question:"Can I contact my personal lawyer on an emergency basis?",
        answer:"The plan includes access to legal advice, consultations, drafting, representing the case in court that are within the scope of your chosen plan.",
    },
    {
        question:"Does the personal lawyer handle cases in court or only offer legal advice?",
        answer:"Your personal lawyer provides legal advice and represents you in court.",
    },
    {
        question:"Is my information safe and confidential with Medence?",
        answer:"Yes, your information is secure and treated with the utmost confidentiality. We adhere to strict privacy policies to ensure that your legal matters and personal data are protected.",
    },
]


export const legalFaq = [
    {
        question:"What if I move to another city?",
        answer:"Even if you move to another city it wont hamper any legal proceedings against your landlord and you wouldn't be required to fly back to your previous city for proceedings."
    },
    {
        question:"Do I have to be involved in day to day operations like visiting courts etc?",
        answer:"No there wouldn't be any need for you to visit courts. All process is taken care by your personal lawyer from start to finish."
    },
    {
        question:"Do you do for both flats and PGs?",
        answer:"Yes we do it for both tenants in both residential flats and PGs."
    },
    {
        question:"Will there by any personal threats from landlords and his goons?",
        answer:"There wouldn't be any threat from landlord as that would only add criminal liability on your landlord and risk his income altogether."
    },
    {
        question:"What if the timelines are exceed in this whole process?",
        answer:"Timelines are strictly pre-decided and executed. Any extension of timeline due to reasons arising due to your personal lawyer will be monetarily compensated based on our agreed terms and conditions."
    },
    {
        question:"Why are your timelines long?",
        answer:"We understand timelines might seem long but most of it is due to situation beyond our control. This is because Indian judiciary is heavily burdened resulting in the problem of long duration proceedings. Rest assured, we ensure for the shortest duration possible to secure your refund. Your personal lawyer's incentives are aligned with your incentives to quickly solve the case and not drag it like it happens with other 'typical' lawyers."
    },
    {
        question:"Do you solve any other problems of tenants apart from security deposits?",
        answer:"While our primary focus is on security deposit issues, we also solve other problems like unfair eviction or frequent privacy intrusions by your landlord."
    },
    {
        question:"Is this plan yearly or monthly? What if I stay for more than one year in the same?",
        answer:"Answer: The pricing and plans are for one-time basis. Even if you stay for less than 1 year or more than 1 year, the pricing remains the same. We aim to standardise pricing for transparency and predictability."
    },
    {
        question:"Why are your plans so cheap?",
        answer:"We have deigned our system on the basis of aggregation, which ensures operational efficiencies along with high rewards for lawyers to attract top talent."
    },
    {
        question:"Is this like insurance?",
        answer:"Not exactly — we’re not an insurance company. But you can think of us as legal protection for your money. For a small one-time fee, you get lawyer-backed support to recover your deposit — often worth 5 to 20 times what you paid us."
    },
]

export const GeneralFaq = [
    {
        question:'What is "Personal lawyer" service by Medence?',
        answer:"Medence's Personal Lawyer service offers you access to a dedicated lawyer for legal advice and support. This lawyer will assist with a wide range of legal concerns, guiding you through legal processes and offering solutions based on your needs."
    },
    {
        question:"Are you an insurance company?",
        answer:"No, Medence is not an insurance company. However, we provide personalized legal services by connecting you with experienced lawyers on a subscription-based plan so that you don’t have to worry about any unforeseen legal expenses."
    },
]

export const Planfaq = [
    {
        question:"What are included and excluded in the plan?",
        answer:"The plan includes access to legal advice, consultations, drafting, and representing the case in court that are within the scope of your chosen plan."
    },
    {
        question:"Does the plan also include my family members? ",
        answer:"The plans are designed for individuals. However, you can avail a discounted rate for your spouse, which also covers children under 18 years."
    },
    {
        question:"Why is the plan pricing so affordable while lawyers outside charge so high?",
        answer:"Medence provides affordable pricing by leveraging a scalable model that enables us to offer legal services at a lower cost while maintaining high-quality expertise. Our focus is on providing value to customers without the high overhead costs associated with traditional law firms."
    },
    {
        question:"Can I upgrade and downgrade my plan later?",
        answer:"Yes, you can upgrade or downgrade your plan as per your needs. Simply contact our support team, and we will assist you with the changes."
    },
    {
        question:"Is there any refund if I don’t like the plan?",
        answer:"We strive to provide you with the best service, but if you are dissatisfied, we offer a refund policy within a specified period after your purchase."
    },
]

export const Lawyerfaq = [
    {
        question:"Does the personal lawyer handle cases in court or only offer legal advice?",
        answer:"Your personal lawyer provides legal advice and represents you in court."
    },
    {
        question:"Is my personal lawyer part of your in-house team?",
        answer:"Your personal lawyer is part of Medence’s external partners and not part of the in-house legal pool."
    },
    {
        question:"What if I don’t like my personal lawyer?",
        answer:"If you are not satisfied with your personal lawyer, you can request a change. We assure to work with you to find a better match for your needs."
    },
    {
        question:"How to reach my personal lawyer?",
        answer:"You can contact your personal lawyer directly via phone, email, or through the Medence platform. We ensure easy and accessible communication for all your legal concerns."
    },
    {
        question:"Can I contact my personal lawyer on an emergency basis?",
        answer:"Yes, you can reach your personal lawyer for urgent matters. However, please note that response times may vary depending on the severity of the situation."
    },
    {
        question:"On what basis is my personal lawyer assigned to me?",
        answer:"Your personal lawyer is assigned based on your specific needs, the complexity of the potential legal issue, the expertise required, and your geographical area. We aim to match you with the most qualified lawyer for your situation."
    },
]

export const BillingFaq = [
    {
        question:"Do I have to pay additional money when I utilize my personal lawyer services during the plan period?",
        answer:"No, there is no additional money involved in utilizing the services of your personal lawyer in your chosen plan."
    },
]

export const OtherFaq = [
    {
        question:"Is my information safe and confidential with Medence?",
        answer:"Yes, your information is secure and treated with the utmost confidentiality. We adhere to strict privacy policies to ensure that your legal matters and personal data are protected."
    },
    {
        question:"What is the process if I have a legal problem?",
        answer:"If you have a legal problem, simply reach out to your assigned personal lawyer. Your lawyer will guide you through the next steps and provide advice or assistance as needed."
    },
    {
        question:"What if I shift my residential location during the purchase of the plan?",
        answer:"If you move to a new location, you can continue using your Medence services. However, please notify us, as we may recommend adjustments to your legal team based on the new jurisdiction or laws relevant to your new location."
    },
]